<resources>
    <string name="app_name">পালাও করোনা</string>
    <string name="app_name_top_bar">পালাও করোনা !</string>

    <string name="feature_01_about_corona">About COVID-19</string>
    <string name="feature_02_test">Virus Test</string>
    <string name="feature_03_news">Recent News</string>
    <string name="feature_04_dos">DOs &amp; DONT\'s</string>
    <string name="feature_05_quarantine">Quarantine</string>
    <string name="feature_06_faq">FAQ</string>
    <string name="feature_07_discussion">Live Updates</string>
    <string name="feature_08_emergency">Emergency &amp; Others</string>

    <string name="okay">Okay</string>
    <string name="lang">বাংলা</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>

    <string name="enter_your_phone_number">Your Phone Number Please?</string>
    <string name="please_enter_your_mobile_number">Please enter your mobile number to receive a verification code and proceed with the test</string>
    <string name="mobile_number">Mobile Number</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>

    <string-array name="genders">
        <item>Male</item>
        <item>Female</item>
        <item>Other</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="verify">Verify</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="personal_phone_optional">Home Phone Number (Optional)</string>
    <string name="gender">Gender</string>
    <string name="age">Age</string>
    <string name="pref_name" translatable="false">corona_pref</string>
    <string name="start_taking_test">Start Taking Test</string>

    <string name="faq_q_1">What are the initial symptoms of COVID-19?</string>
    <string name="faq_q_2">When should you consult a doctor?</string>
    <string name="faq_q_3">What are the emergency signs of COVID-19?</string>
    <string name="faq_q_4">Is COVID-19 contagious?</string>
    <string name="faq_q_5">What is Quarantine?</string>
    <string name="faq_q_6">Should I wear a mask?</string>
    <string name="faq_q_7">Should I use soaps, hand-sanitizers or hand wash?</string>
    <string name="faq_a_1">Symptoms for COVID-19 may appear from 2-14 days after exposure which conclude:\n
                            · Fever\n
                            · Cough\n
                            · Shortness of breath or difficulty in breathing\n
                            · Tiredness\n
                            · Aches\n
                            · Runny nose\n
                            · Sore throat
    </string>
    <string name="faq_a_2">If you have a travel history in the affected places or you are having those symptoms, you should immediately seek help from a professional.</string>
    <string name="faq_a_3">If you are already a Coronavirus disease patient and you are not taking proper medical help, you may go into a critical condition with these signs:
                            · Bluish face or eyes\n
                            · Breathing difficulty\n
                            · Chest pain
    </string>
    <string name="faq_a_4">Yes, it is. The Coronavirus spread from person to person. This is why it is strictly prohibited to make physical contact with the affected patient.</string>
    <string name="faq_a_5">Quarantine is a period of isolation. If you have initial symptoms of this virus you should keep yourself away from any kind of social gathering to find out if you are actually affected or not.</string>
    <string name="faq_a_6">If you have symptoms of the illness or you are treating the patients with COVID-19, you should wear a mask.</string>
    <string name="faq_a_7">You can use either soaps or hand wash. Wash your hands for 20 seconds. If you do not have any of these, you should rub your hand with hand-sanitizer that has 60% alcohol in it.</string>



    <!-- temporary resources -->
    <string name="medium_lorem_ipsum" translatable="false">Quisque imperdiet nunc at massa dictum volutpat. Etiam id orci ipsum. Integer id ex dignissim</string>
    <string name="long_lorem_ipsum" translatable="false">
        বিশ্ব স্বাস্থ্য সংস্থা বলছে, ভাইরাসটির ইনকিউবেশন পিরিয়ড ১৪দিন পর্যন্ত স্থায়ী থাকে। তবে কিছু কিছু গবেষকের মতে এর স্থায়িত্ব ২৪দিন পর্যন্ত থাকতে পারে।\n\n
মানুষের মধ্যে যখন ভাইরাসের উপসর্গ দেখা দেবে তখন বেশি মানুষকে সংক্রমণের সম্ভাবনা থাকবে তাদের। তবে এমন ধারণাও করা হচ্ছে যে নিজেরা অসুস্থ না থাকার সময়ও সুস্থ মানুষের দেহে ভাইরাস সংক্রমিত করতে পারে মানুষ।
শুরুর দিকের উপসর্গ সাধারণ সর্দিজ্বর এবং ফ্লু’য়ের সাথে সাদৃশ্যপূর্ণ হওয়ায় রোগ নির্ণয়ের ক্ষেত্রে দ্বিধাগ্রস্থ হওয়া স্বাভাবিক।</string>
    <string name="phone_number_invalid">Invalid Phone Number. Please enter a valid phone number.</string>
    <string name="invalid_otp">Invalid OTP. Please enter the 6 digits OTP.</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="choose_an_option">Choose an option</string>
    <string name="form_not_completed">Please give answer of all questions</string>
    <string name="give_otp_code">Please check your phone and give your verification code below</string>
    <string name="double_press_to_exit">Press again to exit</string>


</resources>
